pricesinindia.net 2014-06-14

# Privacy Policy | 14th June 2014

PriceInIndia.net is a company which focuses on the electronic products that reviews the consumer product and does provide the information related to the product’s features, specifications, pricing etc.  We take utmost pride in providing perfect privacy for the end user and visitors of the site.

### **Information Gathered from you**

When you subscribe to our site, you will be providing us with your email id, so that the information could be sent to you regarding the product which you have inquired about. The details of the interaction between us will be recorded for further correspondence. Time to time, we will be requesting you to provide your valuable feedback for the products you choose so that the information can benefit other user.

### **IP Address**

IP addresses are collected as they are beneficial to track down the number of users who have visited the website and for providing the statistical data to our marketing staff to reveal the traffic on the site. But we insure that no information regarding you as a user will be violated.

### **Purpose of Information gathered**

Information gathered is utilized in an appropriate manner so that consumers could benefit from it. It is used to provide appropriate and relevant information related to the product for which enquiry has been made. We keep the details of what you have been looking for on our site and keep you updated regarding the same. We do take care of the contracts which you   have signed while getting registered on our site. We do take privilege in getting the feedback from you so that the site could be updated accordingly as per your requirement. Keep you abreast about the changes which have been taking place on the site. If you have subscribed for any newsletter then we insure that the information related to your interest is provided to you on the email id as per record.

### **Rights which are possessed by you**

We ensure that the personal information which has been provided by you is not revealed to our marketing team. In case we intend to do so, we will intimate our users and take your permission before taking a step. When the permission is granted by you then only your information will be provided for marketing purpose. Under certain circumstances some links could be provided on the site, in that case we cannot take full authority of protecting your privacy as every link provided does have their own privacy policy. It is entirely the responsibility of the user and is to their discretion to protect it. It’s recommended that before presenting the information on the link provided, you should go through their privacy policy.

### **Frequent Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

Due to changes in rules and regulations, the privacy policy keeps on changing frequently.  This page will be regularly updated to keep you abreast of any changes in the policy mentioned.

### **Contact**

Any further queries related to the Privacy Policy could be forwarded to [techpluto@gmail.com](mailto:techpluto@gmail.com) and we are sure to get back to you with a solution.
